ROMANCE WITH A SOCK! A fighting fool in the ring...until
a dame lands with a right to the heart.
The Duke Comes Back is a action, romance film directed by Irving Pichel.
After winning the heavyweight championship, boxer Duke Foster (Allan Lane)
quits the ring to marry socialite Susan Corbin (Heather Angel).
When his businessman father-in-law Arnold (Frederick Burton) loses his
fortune, Duke returns to the ring to raise money for him.
Susan is furious that Duke is breaking his promise never to box again, and the stakes
get even higher when a crooked promoter orders him to take a dive ...
Duke Foster, played by Allan Lane.
Susan Foster, played by Heather Angel.
Pauline Corbin, played by Genevieve Tobin.
Barney, played by Ben Welden.
Arnold Corbin, played by Frederick Burton.
Jimmy Foster, played by Johnny Russell.
The Duke Comes Back is a 1937 American drama film directed
by Irving Pichel and written by Adele B.
Buffington and Edmund Seward.
It is based on the 1933 novel The Duke Comes Back by Lucian Cary.
The film stars Allan Lane, Heather Angel and Genevieve Tobin.
It was released on November 29, 1937, by Republic Pictures.
The tone is emotional.